(Sheldon:)Eh... maybe it's your voice.
(Sheldon:)I'm gonna see if I can get James
Earl Jones to do it in post.
(chuckles)
Ooh.
(Bernadette:)Wow.
It's... it's-it's beautiful.
(Howard:)Actually,
it's making me dizzy.
(Leonard:)Good, it's not just me.
(chuckles)
CLAIRE:
Hello.
(Raj:)Hey, Claire.
(Claire:)Hey, what's up?
(Raj:)Hi, yeah.
(Raj:)Um, I was wondering,
(Raj:)if you're free Saturday night,
(Raj:)all my friends are
going to a wine tasting.
(Claire:)Sure, I guess.
(Claire:)If you don't think meeting
your friends is too big a step.
(Raj:)Why would it be too big a step?
(Claire:)I don't know. I just don't
want things to get weird.
(Raj:)Nothing to worry about.
(Raj:)People meet people all the time,
(Raj:)and it isn't weird.
(Raj:)I met Bon Jovi once, which
you'd think might be weird.